greenlaneseo.com 2019-08-01

# Privacy Policy | Greenlane

Effective Date: 11/2016

Last Updated: 6/2018

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When communicating through our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. This could be via our contact forms or mailing list forms. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We collect no financial data.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads across the internet. Google’s use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on past website visits. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [DoubleClick opt-out page](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en#display_optout). Greenlane at any given time may use this technology to serve banner and search ads. Greenlane also manages this technology for our clients.

Information on Google’s Personalized Advertising Policy can be found here: <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/143465>

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways. Please note, your information is never sold. Mailing list information is shared with our email vendor [AWeber](https://www.aweber.com/).

  * To communicate with users or include them in our mailing list distribution.
  * To deliver marketing, advertising or other campaigns to you.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. Any supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into a database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any personally identifiable information, with the exception of name and email through your submission on our email forms. This information is stored via [AWeber](https://www.aweber.com/), and used only to send marketing emails from Greenlane. To opt-out from our AWeber mailing list, please follow these steps: <https://help.aweber.com/hc/en-us/articles/204032336-How-can-I-unsubscribe-from-someone-s-list->

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not aim to collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website advertising are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

2550 Eisenhower Avenue, A203, Eagleville, PA 19403 – (610) 973-7119

United States
